prmdeal.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy - PrmDeal.com

### Privacy Statement

This document explains how we collect, use, and protect your privacy at Prmdeal.com. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This Privacy Statement only covers the site Prmdeal. 

### Aggregated Information

Aggregated information, such as which page users access or visit, and information volunteered by users is collected through various methods. For example, Prmdeal collects IP addresses; an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers (the computers that "serve up" Web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address; when you request a page from Prmdeal, our servers log your IP address. 

Prmdeal only uses IP addresses for the purposes of Web traffic analysis and trends.

### Use of Information

Prmdeal collect, store, share and use information collected from third parties. While we do not collect or store password from third-party service providers, we may receive or store tokens, which allow us to link your Prmdeal account with the third-party service provider. We utilize the information we collect about our users to learn more about how they interact with our Services to customize the Services to their interests and enhance the user experience. Other websites that may be accessible through links from our Services may have their own privacy statements and personal information collection, use, and disclosure practices. Our merchants and business partners also have their own privacy statements, too. Prmdeal undertakes to work with third parties who protect and respect your privacy. 

### Intellectual Property Rights

Except for User Submissions, all of the content, arrangement and layout of the Sites and Services, including, but not limited to, any trademarks, service marks, text, images and other content or copyrightable material, and the compilation of the foregoing (collectively, the “Content”) are the sole and exclusive property of Prmdeal. Any unauthorized use of the Content or Prmdeal Marks is strictly prohibited and may violate civil or criminal laws, including, but not limited to, copyright laws, trademark laws, and the laws of privacy and publicity. 

### Use of Cookies

Prmdeal uses cookies for this site. A cookie is a small data file that most major websites write to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow Prmdeal to measure activity on the site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences. 

### Children and Privacy

Prmdeal encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children. 

### Links to Other Sites

Prmdeal contains links to sites other than Prmdeal; those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as Prmdeal. 

### Effect of Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. Prmdeal reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time and users will be notified of any changes made. 

### Policy Change Notification

If we change any portion of our policy in the ongoing development of our Web site, these changes will be posted at this page and the date the policy has been updated will be reflected at the bottom of the page. Under the circumstance that any change is made to the collection or distribution of personal information, we will attempt notify you via email if it has been collected. 

### Contact Us

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy. You can reach us via the following address: prmdeal@gmail.com 

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR CONSENT TO THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.
